Presented by CJ Entertainment Inc . , and Barunson Co . , Ltd .
A Barunson Film Division production
In this world ,
in an unimaginably strange place ,
a deep forest that we could suddenly fall into
exists somewhere out there .
Everything
started in this deep dense forest .
CHUN Jeong-myoung
EUN Won-jae
SHIM Eun-kyung
JIN Ji-hee
directed by YIM Phil-sung
Our products are a bit unique
so young consumers love it .
Sir , hold on , I got a call .
Hello ?
Why didn 't you answer your phone ?
How do you feel ?
I 'm going to the hospital today .
Hae-young .
I already told you .
When ? When did you tell me ?
Why are you so indifferent ?
I 've been pregnant for four weeks .
I told you a hundred times already .
I 'm not an irresponsible person .
Then what am I ?
What am I doing now ?
If you 're not irresponsible ,
why am I responsible for everything ?
And do you have to go there at a time like this ?
Hae-young !
How much farther do we have to go ?
Not much farther .
We 're almost there .
I guess it 'll be hard to get out of the forest tonight .
Anyway , what 's your name ?
Young-hee , Kim Young-hee .
Your name ?
Eun-soo , Lee Eun-soo .
What kind of name is that for a guy ?
So , why are you out alone this late ?
Won 't your Mom and Dad get mad at you ?
I came out to look for my sister 's hairpin .
It 's a long story .
Anyway , where could it be ?
We 're almost there .
Wow !
Is that really your house ?
House of Happy Children
By the way ,
aren 't you scared to live out here ?
Not at all .
This place is comfortable for us .
Young-hee , make sure you tell Mom before you go out to the forest .
Sorry to trouble you so late .
That 's okay . It 's a pleasure to meet you .
Oh my , you 're seriously injured .
Anyway , we welcome you to our home .
Is he sleepy ?
Looks like it .
I 'd like to introduce you to our children .
This is Man-bok , my eldest son .
He turned thirteen this year .
This is my daughter Jung-soon .
She 's our youngest . She 's seven , but a little weak .
And this is Young-hee .
Oh yeah , you two already met .
This little lady surprises us at times with her late night walks .
Our kids are so adorable , aren 't they ?
Yes .
Excuse me , can I use your phone ?
My cell phone isn 't working .
I 'm sorry , our phone got disconnected a few days ago .
We 've already reported it , but no one 's come by yet .
They 'll probably be here tomorrow .
Right , Man-bok ?
Honey , he looks very exhausted .
Did you clean up the room upstairs ?
Of course , blankets , comforter , it 's all ready .
Looks like you need some rest .
You 've walked a long way . Please go upstairs and rest .
Day One
Low Battery
Out of Service Range
Tada !
Let 's eat . I 'm sure you must be starving .
We sometimes eat like this . The kids love to eat this way .
Very nice . All you need now are birthday candles .
Aren 't you eating ?
We ate already . Please help yourself .
Okay .
Is the phone still not working ?
Well , it 's still early .
Actually , I was on an important call when I had the accident .
My mother 's state is critical so I was in a rush to go to her .
Your mother 's state is critical ?
It means that his mother could pass away .
How could a mother pass away ?
Because she 's very old and sick .
It 's okay .
I 'm not that close to my mother .
Having a mother is nice .
You 'll know when you grow up .
There are people close to your mother .
And those who aren 't .
Having a mother is nice .
A mother is the best thing in this world .
Of course . A mother is the best for a child .
What our Man-bok said is right , don 't you agree ?
I 'm sorry . I was out of place .
I 'm sorry , Man-bok . You 're right .
Thank you for the meal . I really have to go now .
Hello ? Anybody here ?
This is crazy .
I went the way you told me .
But I couldn 't get out of the forest .
And it suddenly got dark .
Since we 're so deep in the forest ,
it gets dark quickly when it 's even slightly cloudy .
We should 've gone with you .
I 'm sorry for being a burden again .
Since I haven 't called ,
my girlfriend will probably have a fit .
You have to help me tomorrow .
It 's so easy to get lost here if you 're alone .
So when you go to work tomorrow I 'd like to go with you .
But I 'm on vacation .
What about you , ma 'am ?
Don 't you go to the market ?
I beg you .
I bet it 's hard to go to the market .
Everyone says that .
But you can get whatever you want at anytime .
Really ?
Then let 's all of us go into town tomorrow .
Sorry , but my youngest is a bit sick .
That 'll be a bit difficult .
Why don 't you go and get some rest ?
What about the way out ?
I will take you .
That 's okay with you , right ?
I know the way , too . I want to go .
Me , too . Me , too .
Okay , let 's go together , you angels .
- He called us angels . - He called us angels .
Is this place some Bermuda Triangle ?
I feel stuffy !
Feel better after throwing that ?
Throw that too while you 're at it .
- Think I can 't , huh ? - Go ahead ! Do it !
Then what ?
I can 't stay here like this forever !
Then what are you going to do ?
I can 't stay here anymore .
What about me ?
What do you want me to do ?
Be quiet !
The kids might hear us .
Who is it ?
Young-hee ?
Sleepwalking ?
She walks in her sleep sometimes with her eyes open .
Mister .
Why do you care when you 're not even our Dad ?
Just call me Eun-soo . Think of me as your brother .
Eun-soo , we 're wide awake thanks to you .
How about we try this ?
We count in our heads .
One sheep , two sheep .
Three sheep , four sheep .
Mister .
Yes ?
What about puppies ?
Puppies ? You waited for puppies ?
One puppy .
No .
White puppy .
White puppy ?
Okay .
One white puppy .
Two white puppies .
Three white puppies .
Four white puppies .
Day Two
What 's the matter ?
What 's going on ?
Where 's Mom and Dad ?
We had urgent business to tend to .
Please look after the kids for a few days .
From Mom and Dad ?
Just a moment .
I need time to think , so let 's be quiet .
Please be quiet !
If you don 't , I 'll punish you !
I 'm sorry .
It 's not because of you all .
I 'll do it .
Let 's eat .
Man-bok , can you take me into town ?
I can 't leave the others .
Jung-soon can 't go far because she 's weak .
Also , I have to study with Young-hee in the morning .
If we can 't go together , can you at least show me a shortcut ?
Once I get to town , I 'll find someone to take care of you all .
He seems nice , doesn 't he ?
For now .
Who 's there ?
Is someone there ?
Someone else lives in these woods , don 't they ?
No .
I 'm certain I saw someone .
I fell after I ran after him .
You 're going to stay here , right ?
What about the phone ?
Eun-soo .
Think about it .
The phone is disconnected , so how 'd we get someone to fix it ?
No one probably called for help .
Where 's the phone ?
Eun-soo !
Are you going to leave us ?
No way .
If you lose the way in the forest , itjust gets deeper .
Was it too deep ?
If I follow the directions you give me ,
I can surely leave the forest , right ?
That 's why ...
You should have marked your way with breadcrumbs .
Mom and Dad went very far away .
Very far away .
They went to the hospital because Mom 's sick .
There 's no hospital around here .
Right , they should have .
Then this would all make sense .
Don 't touch our stuff .
What are you doing here ?
Someone else is here .
What ?
I saw someone with my own two eyes .
Look , nobody 's here .
Someone was definitely in here .
You chicken .
Man-bok .
Please help me .
No matter what happens tomorrow I have to get out .
How ?
It 's a present .
You seemed to have missed your Mom very much .
The Way Out
Day Three
No , you can 't go .
Are you coming from the town ?
Is there a faster way ?
You can 't go . It 's snowing too much .
We 've lost our way , too .
Our car broke down on the highway .
Then don 't come this way .
I heard there 's a house that way .
We need to get out of the snow first .
How 'd you know that there 's a house ?
He told me .
He said his house is over there .
Go back the way you came .
Don 't go , Uncle !
What 's the matter with him ?
Where are your parents ?
They went far away for a little while .
So you 're all alone in this house .
These belong to you ?
We have lots of them .
Really ?
Then ,
there must be a pumpkin wagon and red shoes somewhere .
Kids shouldn 't play with expensive toys .
Your necklace is very pretty .
It keeps snowing .
What is your Uncle going to do ?
If you don 't listen to me ,
I 'm gonna punish you really bad .
I 'll rip all your guts out and throw them in the forest .
You 'll hate that , right ?
Then die ! Die !
Go ahead and die !
Don 't go .
Uncle !
Stop playing with me !
Why aren 't you letting me out ?
Don 't yell .
It 's scary .
Please go and rest .
You 're wet .
This is yours , right ?
Where did you find it ?
All this was due to His will .
Your coming home is His will .
I 'm Deacon Byun .
The kids already told me your name . Eun-soo ?
Your great Holiness
In my soul ...
It keeps snowing .
The snow keeps falling on my desperate hope .
Day Four The snow keeps falling on my desperate hope .
You made all this food yourselves ?
How could you make all this ?
Please feed me .
You 're not a baby . Do it yourself .
No , feed me .
I told you already .
You have to eat yourself .
It hurts .
Your Mom and Dad must 've spoiled you a lot .
That 's enough .
What would these little angles know ?
Now that 's enough from everyone .
Santa Claus is going to grant every kid 's wish
on Christmas day tomorrow .
The Christmas mood this year ahead of the long holidays
is getting more exciting than ever .
Why does everybody like Christmas ?
When Christmas comes ,
Santa Claus grants all the children 's wishes .
I want a magic box
that will give me whatever I want .
Sweet cakes , candy , chocolate , robots , pens .
I want every toy in the world .
Oh , it 's lovely Young-hee .
Is your Uncle very sick ?
Yes , I think he has a cold .
Is that right ?
There 's a stain .
You scared me .
What are you doing here ?
They seemed to have been left here alone for a while .
I just felt bad for them .
You can 't take anything from here .
Not going anywhere ?
Still snowing outside ?
Hansel and Gretel
Once upon a time in the thick deep forest ...
Did you touch my stuff again ?
What the hell is this crap ?
Give it !
Give it to me now !
Son of a bitch .
What did you say to me ?
Let go !
Eun-soo , let 's go out and make a snowman .
Please don 't make him mad .
Forgive me .
Please forgive me .
Who are you ?
What happened to you ?
Please be quiet .
We 'll be in big trouble if the kids find us .
And I 'm not their mother .
What ?
What are you talking about ?
Our car broke down in the middle of the road ,
and we were looking for help .
And then I met Jung-soon . That 's all .
You can 't get out of here no matter how hard you try .
Please don 't tell the children .
What the hell are they ?
They took my husband away .
I don 't know where he is .
I hid here after the sun went down .
This attic is a maze , like the forest .
Look .
It 's useless .
There 's no way to get back .
That child .
He 's here .
Where are you ?
We have to get out of here .
Please help .
Day Five
Where did it go ?
Did you see my ring ?
Did you mistake it for your toy ?
I don 't know where it is .
Come on , I know you do .
Our angels have a lot of those things .
He doesn 't like angels who lie .
Words don 't seem to get through to you .
This lady bothers me !
Man-bok , she 's not right !
I can 't stand her !
Give it a break .
Don 't interfere and go get some fresh air .
I 'll find it myself .
Hurry !
Okay , I 'm going .
I 'm going .
Tell me again what you just said .
I don 't like you !
Leave them alone .
You took it , didn 't you ?
You make me sick .
What did you just say ?
You little brat .
What are you staring at ?
All kids with no parents are brats .
So you all better ...
Man-bok ! Stop it !
Man-bok !
They 're all devils .
It happened because you lost your temper first .
What a sight it was .
I told you what he did to me .
Don 't you trust me ?
Be patient .
I feel like I got a calling .
Something 's evil about this house .
Let 's get out of here .
Calm down .
There are only a lost baby sheep and kids in this deep forest .
Thank you for hugging Jung-soon .
Young-hee .
What 's going on in this house ?
You can tell me , right ?
It tickles .
I really have to go now .
You hate us that much ?
Why do you keep wanting to leave ?
Can 't you just stay with us ?
Young-hee .
What are you doing over there ?
She hit me .
I really hate her .
Don 't you ?
Where are you ?
The Final Day
- Young-hee ! - Hurry , Jung-soon !
Hurry !
Play with us , okay ?
Play with us .
How ?
I love listening to old stories .
Me , too .
All stories have a happy ending .
And the main character gets her wish .
Please tell us a story that you know .
Hurry ! Hurry !
Now listen carefully .
Long , long time ago ,
there lived a Queen .
She had a very cute son .
But her husband , the King ,
was ill and had passed away .
What ? He shouldn 't die early .
I 'm sure he went to a good place .
For instance ,
like heaven ?
Heaven is a place like this .
Probably .
Hurry , then what happened ?
So the King went to heaven .
And his kingdom disappeared .
So the Queen
sent her son to a palace where there were only children .
People called the place ...
The Kingdom of Angels .
Wow , so every child had wings and flew ?
But the Master of the palace ,
didn 't like little angels .
He started to punish the children without any reason .
He was a real scary person .
Why didn 't the Queen come back for her son ?
She came looking for him .
But he couldn 't be the same
because of his memory of being abandoned .
So the boy who became a prince ,
left the palace one day .
And he met his princess from a neighboring kingdom .
And they lived happily ever after .
Right ?
No .
A baby was born in the womb of the princess .
The day the prince found out
he heard that his mother became ill .
So he passed by a thick forest
to go see his mother .
But the wagon the prince was riding in fell over a rock .
A fairy approached the prince while he was lying down .
The injured prince went to a magical castle with the fairy .
A magic castle
that he couldn 't leave from .
But ...
The fairies in the castle
didn 't want him to leave .
Right ?
If the prince doesn 't leave to go to his princess ,
the baby could die .
And he can 't nurse his ill mom .
But the fairies
could do anything with their imagination .
The prince already fell in love with the fairies .
So everybody
lived happily ever after .
The end .
Isn 't that right , Uncle ?
I found it in the back .
But the prince found out a scary secret about the fairies .
And the fairies weren 'tjust nice .
The prince kept trying to leave the castle .
The fairies got mad .
So they chopped off his arms and legs so that he couldn 't leave .
Like that !
Have you seen Kyung-sook ?
The woman I came here with .
She 's disappeared with some valuable things .
She 'll be back soon .
It 's hard to find your way alone in these deep woods .
And the snow hasn 't melted yet .
So what happed next in your story ?
I don 't know .
I don 't remember .
Look here , Uncle .
I have to find my beloved angel who 's lost her way .
How about going into the woods with me ?
Where the hell is she ?
Uncle .
This isn 't the time to fool around .
This is no joke .
I swear she was here .
This house is really fun .
Sometimes you run into some very interesting things .
I just thought of something .
I ought to just take over this house for Him .
I 'm going to be real deacon of this house .
You 'll regret this .
She didn 't run away .
There 's something else in this house .
We could rot in here forever .
Do you get me ?
You should be a little nice in the way you speak to me , boy .
So then , you mean there 's something else about those kids .
Look here .
A child and the devil are raised the same .
If the angels interfere with His business ,
then I 'll just send them back to where they came from .
You know heaven , right ?
What the hell are you ?
I told you to talk to me with respect , you bastard !
There 's no exception for anyone who interferes with His business .
Understand ?
My lost young sheep ?
So when did you start living here ?
Long , long time ago .
That long ago ?
How long ? As long as your age ?
By the way ,
your parents seem to be very good people .
To think about
building this big pretty house deep in the forest .
This is very special .
So what I mean
is that your parents built this nice house .
So they must 've left a lot of valuable things for you , right ?
Since they 've been gone for a while ,
you have to buy a lot of food , toys ,
and give offerings to the church , right ?
We don 't need that stuff .
We have all that we want .
We can get whatever we want with our imagination .
You 're absolutely right .
My angles can do whatever they want if they imagine .
You 're right .
Now , I will guard my angels from now on .
Okay ?
Being here without parents ...
Don 't listen to him .
You 're always trying to leave us anyway .
He promised to protect us from now on .
No , you can 't trust him .
Uncle , what are you doing ?
What are you so worried about ?
Your mother upstairs and his wife .
What have you done to all of them ?
Our Mom isn 't here .
She 'll be back later .
She promised me .
We did nothing wrong , Uncle .
We 're not bad kids .
Now that 's enough .
Don 't blame them without any evidence .
Grown-ups are to blame , you know that .
Our angels can do no harm ,
right ?
Uncle shouldn 't be saying that to our innocent angels .
To Jung-soon , my angel .
We made it .
Is it delicious ?
Yes , it is .
It 's impossible .
They 're only kids .
Help me .
Help me ?
Waiting for Mom and Dad
New Mom and Dad ?
Was it fun ?
Kids !
Cut it out .
Help us .
She 's bleeding .
I 'm suffering , too .
Someone has to come by here at some point .
We tried everything . Let 's wait a bit more .
A bit more ? How long do we have to wait ?
I 'm going crazy ! I can 't wait any longer !
Just wait a little more .
Until when ?
How long are you going to wait ? Forever ?
But I didn 't want to show my gift to Mom and Dad .
Since they 'll be too surprised .
Go out again today .
If we get out of here , we 're through .
Okay , let 's do that .
No matter how many times I try it 's useless .
Shall I just burn down the forest ?
You don 't know the way out , right ?
You 'll get lost and scared again anyway .
You always miss your Mom when you panic .
I told you to stop talking about my Mom !
Mommy ...
Shut up !
Let go !
How many times did I tell you not to bring that up !
You know I hate it when you say that !
Man-bok , I can 't stand it anymore .
Honey .
Are you crazy ?
I can 't move my hand .
Man-bok , what shall we do ?
I got caught .
Mom and Dad , you 'll stop fighting now , right ?
I didn 't say anything .
Don 't come any closer .
Don 't raise your voice .
Young-hee thinks this is all a dream .
Try it on .
I wish that would be my doll .
The biggest , prettiest doll in the world .
Good girl .
My baby .
You 're so pretty .
Let me give you a big hug .
Stay by me forever .
The third road to the right .
Once to the left .
Once again to the left .
Don 't I look pretty ?
Why don 't you want to hug me ?
Young-hee , you 're pretty the way you are .
Please be nice to me .
What 's wrong with you ?
Sometimes I have a very scary dream .
A very terrible dream .
He keeps saying that I 'm pretty .
Who keeps saying that to you ?
Did something bad happen to you ?
Why do you keep trying to leave us ?
I like you .
We 're not bad kids .
Plus , you 've already become the hero of our story .
What ?
Didn 't you come here to find it ?
If we just imagine in this room ,
all our wishes will come true .
That 's why I got rid of all the mirrors in this room .
It happens only in this room .
In the forest
Someone 's singing .
The birds are chirping
The stream is peacefully flowing
I praise your almighty power
Year of 1971
Your Greatness
With the angels
I will now carry out Your will .
Amen .
Kim Man-bok , born in 1959
Kim Young-hee , born in 1960
Kim Jung-soon , born in 1965
Is it in here ?
Man-bok , big brother .
Tell me .
There are no documents left in this house .
Don 't touch that .
Free Jung-soon right now !
You 're really scary .
Big brother Man-bok has scary eyes .
Tell me .
Where did your Mom and Dad really go ?
Did that stupid Uncle take off after doing something ?
Or did Man-bok do something to him ?
When I was young ,
I sent my Dad to heaven , you see .
He was annoying me too much .
Man-bok , did you do the same , like me ?
You 're all the same .
I 'm sick of it .
Man-bok , this man is really , really bad .
And he promised to protect us .
Why are all grown-ups bad ?
Man-bok !
What are you ? Satan ?
Satan , leave from here . Satan , leave from here .
Is that why You responded to me ?
Have these Satan children taken over your dwelling place ?
Now , I will retrieve Your home .
Man-bok !
Stop it !
I don 't want you to get hurt !
Man-bok , stop it !
You 'll become the same person if you do this .
Why ?
Why should I spare him ? He 's a bad grown-up .
Bad grown-ups always need to be punished .
But not like this .
There 's surely another way .
Look , they get punished in here .
This is only a story .
No .
This book grants us all our wishes .
Who the hell are you ?
What happened in this house ?
Long time ago ...
We 've lived in here long time ago .
The Home of Happy Children
Father , I was wrong .
Please forgive me .
Father , please forgive me .
Please stop . Please don 't .
Forgive me .
Please stop .
Father .
No .
Why did you come back this time ?
Did you wake up in the middle of the night and scare everyone ?
Or was it because you missed this place ?
Father , I 'm prettier than Jung-soon .
I 'm much prettier than Jung-soon .
She 's too young and skinny .
Please , take me instead , Father .
The Christmas mood this year ahead of the long holidays
is getting more exciting than ever .
Let 's see , it 's Christmas tomorrow .
So why do you like Christmas ?
Because it 's Christmas .
And Santa Claus will grant all the children 's wishes .
Man-bok , does Santa Claus
grant every wish ?
I don 't know .
I don 't know , Jung-soon .
But why hasn 't Santa Claus come to us ?
Because heaven is too far from here .
I hope he comes this year .
You were very good ?
I 've been better .
No , I was more obedient to our parents .
Man-bok .
Jung-soon ?
Time to wake up .
You angels .
Come here .
The children still seem to be sleepy .
Anyway , that 's great of you to see that they rest .
Are these all of the children ?
No , these are the youngest .
The older kids went to the school in town .
This boy came here when he was five .
He got beaten by his father so he 's a bit gloomy .
Oh goodness .
I did my best for him , but it 's not that easy .
As you know , children are influenced by grown-ups .
These two are sisters .
Goodness , they look so alike .
They 'll be so pretty when they grow older .
Of course , they 're just like angels .
Although I 'm a bit worried about the youngest since she 's weak .
So you have something ready for us ?
Kids , it 's Santa Claus .
He came a very long way to see you .
Isn 't that right ?
Look at this .
It looks so delicious .
Good .
Now , eat one .
You have one , too .
Is it delicious ?
Sweet , isn 't it ?
This is for the young little lady .
And this is a special Christmas gift from Santa Claus .
Hansel and Gretel
I 'll bring some more books next time .
Mister .
You 're really Santa Claus , right ?
You 're really Santa , right ?
You 're going to grant all our wishes for Christmas , right ?
Of course .
If you were a very good girl , all your wishes are granted .
Santa , we 're not bad children .
Of course you 're not .
Kids .
I will tell you a secret .
Starting today , if you just imagine it
and want it ,
all your wishes will be granted .
If we just imagine it ?
And want it ?
Of course .
Help me .
I 'm hungry .
Seung-ho ...
Man-bok , why isn 't he moving ?
Hyung-joon .
Eat some of this .
Santa Claus gave it to us .
Wake up .
Wake up !
Your almighty
And great Holiness
Praises my soul
Your almighty and great Holiness
If it weren 't for you all , these sweets would be more delicious .
Bad , very bad .
No , no .
Uncle is the bad one .
He tried to run away from you , remember ?
Right ?
I 'll protect you forever .
No !
Forever .
Man-bok !
I 'll stay by your side !
He 's lying !
It 's a complete lie !
How dare you stare me down !
Shut up , you bastard .
Man-bok !
Eun-soo 's right .
He 's just like the Father at the orphanage .
If I imagine ...
If I really want it ...
All my wishes will come true during Christmas .
Right ?
- Punish him ! Hurry ! - Satan 's children !
What are you doing ?
I 'll burn you all in hell !
Man-bok .
We 'll be happy from now on , right ?
Eun-soo .
Live with us forever .
Forever , okay ?
You have to get out of this curse .
You have to leave this place .
I 'll help you , okay ?
Leave here and make new friends .
Become grown-ups .
We hate grown-ups !
If you keep this up , you 'll be like the bad grown-ups .
No , we 're different .
We thought you 'd be different , but you 're all the same .
If we start to trust and like them ,
they try to leave us .
Let 's see if you can leave this forest .
Please .
You have to go out to the real world .
You have to be happy , too .
What 's it like in your world ?
Can children live happily there ?
Being Happy Forever with Uncle
That 's how Uncle lived with us happily ever after .
And you 've already become the hero of our story .
Our story ends here .
I 've already decided .
I have loved ones waiting for me .
When someone you love is not by your side .
You know how painful and sad that is .
You all know that very well .
Everybody hates us .
They all try to leave us .
We thought you were different .
We thought you really liked us .
Young-hee , let 's get out of here .
Why do you keep wanting to leave ?
We have everything here .
If we just imagine it .
I told you .
My baby prince will be born soon .
That baby needs me .
What about us ?
Who 's going to take care of us ?
We need you .
Forever .
I lived my life thinking I was the only one who was unhappy .
And always tried to get out , including here .
But now ...
Now , I don 't .
We are not bad children .
But everybody
thinks that we are .
Are we really that bad ? Are we ?
Eun-soo !
I 'm sorry .
I 'm really sorry .
What for ?
For all of this .
Eun-soo .
You 're going to take care of us , right ?
You 're going to stay with us , right ?
Let 's leave together .
You don 't know if you haven 't tried .
No .
We can 't leave this place .
This is our home , Eun-soo .
I like you very much .
Your hug feels so warm .
Thank you .
I 'm sorry .
Young-hee , I 'm sorry .
I miss you , Hae-young .
I miss you .
Burn the notebook .
Burn your story in the notebook .
Hurry .
What are you doing ?
Hurry and burn it .
Erase yourself from our memories and our imagination .
Eun-soo , what are you doing ?
You have to take care of us forever .
Bye .
Were you in the car accident ?
How did your car fly all the way over there ?
And where have you been ?
This is so weird .
Are you hurt anywhere ?
Over there !
Try to do a good job , old man .
Wait a minute .
Let 's finish up and go , okay ?
Go buy some powdered milk .
I love you .
I 'm going to bed .
If what happened was just a dream ,
I wouldn 't be curious about the kids and feel sorry for them .
Where on earth was that place ?
Child Murderer Not Found
Byun Ji-wan 's Car Found on Highway 37
Who is Serial Killer Byun Ji-wan ? Deacon of Religious Cult
Highway 37 called 'The Road of Death'
Are all the children there happy ?
Executive producer Miky LEE Co-executive producer CHOl Jae-won
Producers CHOl Jae-won and SEO Woo-sik
Associate producer KANG Young-mo
Screenplay by KIM Min-sook and YIM Phil-sung
Original story by KIM Min-sook
Cinematographer KIM Jee-yong
Lighting director SHIN Sang-yeul
Music director LEE Byeongwoo
Production designer RYU Seong-hee
Editor KIM Sun-min
Costumes CHO Sang-kyung